譯者：微博@Emtee
愛之女巫
譯者:微博@Emtee
我在開啓一段新的生活
I'm starting a new life.
這裏紅杉林立  靜謐又乾淨
Up here where it's quiet and clean among the redwoods.
幾乎沒人認識我
And almost no one knows me.
可憐的杰瑞
Poor Jerry.
他離開我之後 我精神失常了
I had a nervous breakdown after he left me.
他們說 現在我已痊愈
They say I'm cured now.
但我仍有侵入性想法
But I still have intrusive thoughts.
我的治療師告訴我 像我這樣的不在少數
My therapist told me that I'm not unusual at all.
他們遍布世界各地
People are abused all over the world
每天都受淩虐
every day
比我更嚴重
much worse than me
而他們都挺好
and they do fine.
小姐 你的尾燈壞了
Your tail light's out, miss.
謝謝提醒
Thank you for letting me know.
你要給我開罰單嗎
Are you gonna write me a ticket?
這次就算了 但務必修好它
I'll let ya go this time, but make sure you get it fixed.
謝謝 警官
Thank you, officer.
開車注意安全
You drive safely.
杰瑞一離開我 我就傾我所能
When Jerry left me, I devoured everything
瞭解了關于如何俘獲男人的方法
I could about how to get your man back.
據專家所說 男人都很弱
According to the experts, men are very fragile.
只要你會表現自己 他們就會被迷倒
They can get crushed down if you assert yourself in any way.
你得工于心計
You have to be very tricky.
伊蓮?
Elaine?
嗨 我是雀茜
Hi, I'm Trish.
嗨 雀茜 很高興見到你
Hi, Trish, it's nice to meet you.
你真漂亮
You're so pretty.
我沒別的意思
Oh, um, I didn't mean anything.
我已經結婚了
I'm married and everything.
我沒多想
No, I didn't think anything.
我來幫你拎包吧
Well, let me help you with your bags.
就這些嗎
Is this all you've got?
暫時是的
For now.
我的藝術用品之後會被運來
My art supplies are being shipped over later.
你是個藝術家?
So you're an artist?
是的
Yes, I am.
我是個室內裝修師
I'm an interior decorator.
真的?
Oh, really?
沒錯
Yes.
我和芭芭拉就是因爲裝修認識的 我裝修了這套公寓
That's how I met Barbara.I decorated this apartment.
幸好我還留著鑰匙
It was lucky I still had the keys.
芭芭拉完全不清楚自己什麽時候會回來
Barbara didn't exactly know when she'd be back.
你怎麽認識芭芭拉的
How do you know Barbara?
在舊金山時 我們常一起跳舞
We used to dance together in San Francisco.
是嗎
Really?
但願你喜歡這套公寓
Well, I hope you like the apartment.
有點俗艶 但芭芭拉想這樣
It's a bit garish but Barbara wanted it that way.
她讓我用上托特塔羅牌裏的所有顔色
She had me take all of the colors from the Thoth tarot deck
她和她的學生們還畫了一堆玄妙的畫讓我挂
and she and her students did a bunch of occult paintings for me to hang.
她喜歡一切巫術類的東西
She's into all that Wicca stuff.
就是這裏
Well, this is it.
雀茜 我很喜歡
Oh, Trish, I love it.
好美
It's just beautiful.
真的嗎
Really?
很高興你這麽說
Oh, I'm so glad.
我還以爲太過俗艶了
I thought I may have overdone it.
沒有 我就喜歡這樣的
Oh no, it's exactly my taste.
你一定累壞了 想必你想躺下休息了吧
You must be exhausted.I'm sure you want to lie down.
實際上 我想吃點東西
Actually, I was thinking about getting a bite to eat.
這附近你瞭解嗎
Do you know of a place around here?
有家維多利亞式茶館
There's the Victorian tea room.
我們能一起去 你不介意有伴的話
We could go together, if you don't mind the company.
那太好了
Oh, how fantastic.
我能在哪梳洗
Where can I freshen up?
臥室在那邊
The bedroom is through there.
馬上就好
I'll only be a moment.
這地方好漂亮
What a lovely room.
當然啦
Yes, isn't it?
我喜歡維多利亞式的東西
I love Victoriana.
在這裏就像成了童話裏的公主
Being here is like being a Princess in a fairy tale.
伊蓮 你有公主夢嗎
Do you have fairy Princess fantasies, Elaine?
當然
Of course.
我們已是成年女性 但心裏面
We may be grown women, but underneath
我們只是夢想著被白馬王子
we're just little girls dreaming about being carried off
帶走的小女孩
by a prince on a white horse.
或許吧
Yes, I suppose so.
挺荒謬的 不是嗎
It's ridiculous, isn't it?
我想我還沒找到我的白馬王子
I don't think I've found my prince charming yet,
但我想我找到了方法
but I think I found the formula.
我一直在研究超心理學
You know, I've been studying parapsychology
我對男人的瞭解比過去多得多了
and I understand men so much better than I used to.
我以前就那麽瞭解的話
If only I would have known before what I know now.
杰瑞就不會永遠離開我了
Then Jerry would have never left me.
杰瑞是誰
Who's Jerry?
我的前夫
My exhusband.
他離開我的那天就是我死去的日子
The day he left me was the day that I died.
但之後 我重生爲女巫了
But then I was reborn as a witch.
芭芭拉和加恩讓我重生了
Barbara and Gahan brought me back to life.
他們教了我關于魔法和男人的一切
They taught me everything I know about magic and about men.
男人就像孩子一樣
Men are like children.
他們很容易被討好
They're very easy to please
只要我們給他們想要的
as long as we give them what they want.
我們剛說到哪了
Where were we?
對了 男人 你說我們得給他們想要的
Oh, men, you said we need to give them what they want.
男人想要什麽呢
Well, what do men want?
只想要個漂亮女人來愛 但也要能照顧他們
Just a pretty woman to love and to take care of them
能讓他們感覺自己是男人
and to make them feel like a man
能在任何方面給予他們完全的自由
and to give them total freedom in whatever they wanna do or be.
可我們想要的呢
But what about what we want?
如果我們一直滿足他們的需求
How are we going to be equals with men
那怎麽才能男女平等呢
if we keep catering to all of their needs?
我認爲如果你想要愛情 那你就得給予愛情
I think that if you want love, you have to give love.
給予男人性愛是釋放他們潜在感情的一種方式
Giving men sex is a way of unlocking their love potential.
你講得就像你被男權制社會洗腦了似的
You sound as if you'd been brainwashed by the patriarchy.
你的整個自我價值就在于取悅男人
Your whole selfworth is wrapped up in pleasing a man.
我承認我用性愛得到這東西
I'll admit, I used sex to get this,
但我幷不爲此感到驕傲
but I'm not proud of it.
全世界不是圍繞著一個男人的需求轉的
A whole world doesn't revolve around a man's needs.
如果每次理查德想做愛了 我就和他做
If I gave Richard sex every time he wanted it,
那我早殘廢了
I'd be a wreck.
可憐的理查
Poor Richard.
他愛你 也想要你 你却折磨他
He loves you and he wants you and you torture him.
你必須滿足男人的幻想
You have to give a man his fantasy.
男人的幻想?
His fantasy?
沒錯 男人的幻想
Yes, his fantasy.
但我真正感興趣的
But what I'm really interested in
是愛情
is love.
你也許會說我痴迷于愛情
You might say I'm addicted to love.
我好奇是不是所有女人都那麽想
I wonder if all women feel that way?
那要看你說的愛情是什麽意思
Well, it depends on what you mean by love.
丈夫不是王子 伊蓮
A husband isn't a prince, Elaine,
生活也不是童話
and life isn't a fairy tale.
我們必須面對這個事實
We have to face that fact.
爲什麽
Why?
或許你多取悅取悅你丈夫
Maybe life could be a fairy tale
生活就會是童話了
if you pleased your husband more.
我不需要取悅理查德
I don't need to please Richard.
理查德是因爲我這個人而愛我
Richard loves me for myself.
當然
Of course.
可能你確實是找到了你的白馬王子
Maybe you did find your prince charming.
可能確實如此
Perhaps I did.
猜猜是誰
Guess who.
理查德 你怎麽在這
Richard, what are you doing here?
這個茶館僅限女性
This tea room is for ladies only.
我在上班時間去找你了 朱莉說你在這裏
Oh, I went to visit you at work and Julie said you were here.
我本想我們一起吃午餐
I thought we could have lunch together.
很貼心 但我已經吃過午餐了
Well, that's very sweet, but I've already had my lunch.
對了 理查德 這是伊蓮
Oh, uh, Richard, this is Elaine.
伊蓮 這是我的丈夫 理查德
Elaine, this is my husband, Richard.
我聽過很多關于你的事 理查德
I've heard so much about you, Richard.
但願沒有太糟的
Nothing too horrible, I hope.
正相反
On the contrary.
法術書
愛情法術
女神 求你了
Goddess, please,
給我一個英俊 溫柔的男人
send me a beautiful, sweet man
要和我愛他一樣愛我
to love me as I love him.
要愛我 愛我
To love me, love me,
愛我
love me,
love me.
月升草藥
魔法藥店
嗨 你是溫迪嗎
Hi, are you Wendy?
是的 我能爲你做什麽
Yes, what can I do for you?
我是伊蓮
I'm Elaine.
我們通過電話 我是製作手工皂和蠟燭的
We spoke on the phone.I make natural soaps and candles and things.
伊蓮啊 想起來了
Elaine, right.
謝謝來訪
Thanks for coming by.
我能看下嗎
Mind if I have a look?
看吧
Please do.
這些都不錯
These are nice.
愛情魔法
非常不錯
Really nice.
我覺得這些會賣得不錯
I think these will do well in the store.
那你是要了嗎
Then you'll take them?
先賣這些 看看情况
Let's start with these and see how they do.
愛情魔法
伊蓮製造
下周或下下周都賣掉的話 我會訂更多的
If these sell in the next week or two, I'll order more.
怎麽樣
Sound good?
太好了
Yes, fantastic.
謝謝 溫迪
Thank you, Wendy.
不客氣 伊蓮
Sure, Elaine.
祝福你
Bright blessings.
人們總問我 爲什麽我是個女巫
People always ask me why I'm a witch.
我告訴他們 那是因爲我想擁有魔力
I tell them it's because I wanna have magical powers.
但它不是聽上去那麽回事
But it's not like it sounds.
它僅僅是用你的意志去得到你想要的
All it is is using your will to get what you want.
嗨
Hi.
今天天氣真好
It's a beautiful day.
是啊
Yes, it is.
我喜歡在這樣的日子裏體驗大自然
I love to be out in nature on days like this.
你喜歡大自然?
Oh, you like nature?
非常喜歡
Very much.
你看上去也是個喜歡大自然的人
You seem like a nature type too.
我敢打賭你喜歡在樹林裏消磨時間
I'll bet you like to spend time in the woods.
沒錯
That's right.
你怎麽知道
How'd you know?
我能看出來
I can just tell.
大自然是你的心之所在
Nature is where your heart is.
城市和人讓你感到厭煩
City and people can get to be too much for you.
幾秒鐘就從一個人身上看出這麽多了啊
Whuh, that is a lot to get from someone in a few seconds.
我在這方面很有天賦
I'm talented that way.
我對城市的看法 你說得沒錯
Well, you're right about the city.
實際上 我在樹林裏有棟房子 離這裏約一個小時的路程
In fact, I have a house out in the woods about an hour from here.
我有時間了 就喜歡去那裏
I like to go there whenever I can to, you know,
思考 閱讀
just think and read.
你帶你妻子去那裏嗎
Do you take your wife up there?
不帶
No.
我沒結婚
I'm not married.
那你至少會偶爾帶個姑娘去那裏
Well, you might at least take a girl up there once in a while.
沒錯
I do.
沒錯 偶爾
I do, once in a while.
你想現在帶個姑娘過去嗎
You wanna take a girl up there now?
什麽意思
What do you mean?
我剛來這裏
Well, I'm new in town
還沒怎麽體驗過周圍的大自然
and I haven't seen much of the nature around here.
我會給你做一頓好吃的晚餐
I'll make you a nice dinner.
好的 沒問題
Yes, yes, okay, sure.
我的車就在那邊
Uh, my car is right over there.
好的
Okay.
我們走吧
Let's go.
你知道我現在想做什麽嗎
You know what I'd like to do right now?
我想像小孩那樣在車裏做愛
I'd like to make love right here in the car just like we were kids.
等等 等等
Wait, wait.
想喝點嗎
You want some?
這是什麽
What is it?
是我做的
Something I made.
好烈啊
That is, that is strong.
把它喝完
Finish it.
韋恩 韋恩 別這樣
No, Wayne, Wayne, stop.
別在這裏
Not here.
我們進去吧
Let's go inside.
好漂亮
This is beautiful.
我去做晚餐
I'll start the dinner.
看上去很美味
This looks delicious.
敬大自然
To nature.
這樣很棒 對吧
This is really nice, isn't it?
我常在學期末來這裏放鬆
I like to come up here a lot at the end of the semester to unwind.
你是位老師嗎
Are you a teacher?
是啊 我在大學教書
Yeah, I teach at the university.
教什麽的
What do you teach?
英國和法國文學
English and French literature
主要是18世紀的
with a focus on the 18th century.
所以 你一定是個很放蕩的人
So, you must be quite a libertine.
放蕩的人?
A libertine?
你爲什麽會那麽說
Why would you say that?
你知道的
Oh, you know.
所有危險的曖昧關係都是班尼·希爾風格的
All of the dangerous liaisons, Benny hill stuff.
更別說卡薩諾瓦了
Not to mention Casanova.
18世紀的書多著呢
Well, there were a lot of books written in the 18th century.
是真的嗎
Well, is it true?
你是個放蕩的人嗎
Are you a libertine?
是的
Yes I am.
我喜歡女人
I love women.
你介意嗎
Does that bother you?
正相反
On the contrary.
我覺得怪怪的 頭好暈
I feel strange, dizzy.
你給我喝的東西裏有什麽
What was in that drink you gave me?
有機漿果 伏特加 致幻草藥
Organic berries, vodka, hallucinogenic herbs.
致幻草藥?
Hallucinogenic herbs?
寶貝啊
Oh, baby.
你真的很瘋狂
You are really wild.
你介意我讓自己更舒服些嗎
Would you mind if I made myself more comfortable?
完全不介意
Not at all.
什麽情况
What the hell?
你的外套
Your coat.
太亮了
It's so bright.
我總會裱褙我的衣物
I always line my clothing.
你有兩個自我
You have two selves.
你向世界所展現的黑暗與安靜
Dark and quiet that you show the world.
你要把那個給誰
Who do you give that to?
彩虹?
The rainbow?
我要把彩虹給你
I give the rainbow to you.
馬上就給
Right now.
天啊
Oh god.
伊蓮
Oh, Elaine.
看看你啊
Look at you.
現在你能和我做愛了
You can make love to me now.
好了
Okay.
怎麽了 韋恩
What is it, Wayne?
怎麽了 寶貝
What is it, baby?
伊蓮 我感覺好怪
Oh, Elaine, I feel so strange.
沒事的 有我在呢
It's all right, you're with me.
伊蓮
Elaine.
以前從沒女人那樣委身于我
No woman has ever given herself like that to me before.
人生坎坷 對吧
Life has been tough, huh?
某方面來說 是的
Yeah, in a way.
你和我遇見的其他女人不一樣
You're not like any other woman I've met.
不耍手段 沒有企圖
No games, no agendas.
你似乎就是順應人生
You just seem to take life as it is.
還有其他方式對待人生嗎
Is there any other way to take life?
我相處過的女人
Well, the women I've been with,
你一和她們上床 她們就要你對她們做出一堆承諾
they all want you to make a bunch of promises to 'em as soon as you sleep with 'em.
但你怎麽能向自己都不認識的人做出承諾呢
But, how can you commit to someone that you don't even know?
這太瘋狂了
It's crazy.
我懂 寶貝
I know, baby.
我懂
I know.
我從沒想到自己會心有所屬
I never thought I wanted to be tied down to anybody.
但那只是因爲以前從沒遇到完全對的人
But it's just 'cause no one was ever quite right.
那些身體讓我著迷的女人
All the women that I'm attracted to physically
都不够聰慧
they're never bright enough.
而那些聰慧的都相貌平平 不會讓我有欲望
And all the bright ones are homely and don't arouse me.
這似乎是個大問題
That seems like quite a problem.
沒錯
It is.
我覺得我一生都是個獨行者
I feel my whole life as a loner,
認爲自己不需要任何人
thinkin' I didn't need anybody.
但現在我不那麽確定了
But now I'm not so sure.
伊蓮
Oh, Elaine,
我以前從沒感受過真正的愛情
I have never felt real love like this before.
你現在太多愁善感了
You're just having a lot of emotions right now.
伊蓮 我好害怕
Elaine, I'm scared.
我不習慣這種强烈的感覺
I'm not used to feeling things so strongly.
我承受不住 我承受不住
I can't take it, I can't take it.
伊蓮 我病了
Elaine, I'm sick.
我病了
I'm sick.
嘿 沒事的
Hey, it's all right.
有我在呢
I've got you.
我愛你
I love you.
我永遠都會在你身邊
And I'll always be here for you.
睡會兒吧
Try to get some sleep.
伊蓮
Elaine.
伊蓮 你在哪
Elaine, where are you?
真是個娘們兒
What a pussy.
真是個孩子
What a baby.
我還以爲我找到了一個真正的男人
I thought I'd found a real man,
但他就像個小女孩
but he's just like a little girl.
伊蓮！
Elaine!
我哭得撕心裂肺時 可從沒有人在我身邊
No one was ever there for me when I was crying my heart out.
從沒有人安慰過我
No one ever comforted me.
沒有人
No one.
早上好 韋恩
Good morning, Wayne.
嗨 伊蓮
Hi, Elaine.
給 喝吧
Here, drink this.
昨晚我做了個很可怕的夢
I had such horrible dreams last night.
夢到了什麽 寶貝
What did you dream about, baby.
夢到自己在呼喊你的名字
I dreamt that I was calling your name
而你却毫無回應
and you didn't answer.
我不停地呼喊 但我却找不到你
I kept calling and calling, but I couldn't find you.
伊蓮 你愛我的 對嗎
Oh, Elaine, you love me, don't you?
我當然愛你
Of course, I love you.
天呐 伊蓮
Oh god, oh god, Elaine.
你餓嗎
Are you hungry?
我不知道我怎麽了
I don't know what I am.
睡會兒吧
Well, try to get some sleep.
伊蓮
Elaine.
別離開我
Don't leave me.
我哪都不去 寶貝
I'm not going anywhere, baby.
我馬上回來
I'll be right here.
韋恩 醒醒
Wayne, wake up.
不早了
It's late.
韋恩
Wayne.
韋恩 寶貝 醒醒
Wayne, baby, wake up.
醒醒
Wake up.
韋恩
Wayne.
衛生棉條幷不噁心
Tampons aren't gross.
女人會月經 而經血是一樣美麗的東西
Women bleed and that's a beautiful thing.
你知道 很多男人都沒見過一根被用過的衛生棉條嗎
Do you know that most men have ever even seen a used tampon?
部分的我現在可以和韋恩在一起了
Part of me can be with Wayne now.
永遠地
Always.
我真不介意死亡
I don't really mind death.
我以前埋過人
I've buried people before.
是我真正在乎的人
People I really cared about.
不管怎樣 我們最終都會變成肥料
In the end we're all just compost anyway.
一切都會重生
Everything regenerates.
我想重生爲一隻猫
I'd like to come back as a cat.
我的猫死後 我一直很沮喪
I've been so depressed since my cat died.
他叫格雷馬爾金 是黑白色的 他是我最好的朋友
His name was Greymalkin, but he was black and white.He was my best friend.
我要把彩虹給你
I give the rainbow to you.
馬上給你
Right now.
稍等
Just a minute.
嗨 雀茜
Oh hi Trish.
進來吧
Come on in.
嘿 伊蓮
Hey, Elaine.
你看起來美極了
You look gorgeous.
我喜歡你的髮型
I love what you've done with your hair.
謝謝
Thank you.
- 有事嗎 親愛的 - 我一直沒能聯繫到你
- What's up, honey? - Well, I haven't been able to reach you,
所以我想我過來看看一切是否安好
so I thought I'd come over to see if everything was all right.
我很好
I'm fine.
真的
Really.
你要吃點或喝點什麽嗎
Can I offer you something?
我剛沏了茶 做了蛋糕
I just made some tea and cake.
茶就行了 謝謝
Just tea, thank you.
要加奶油和糖嗎
Cream and sugar?
不用 謝了
No, I'm fine, thank you.
你一直都在忙什麽
So, what have you been so busy with?
但願是男人的事
A man, I hope.
沒錯 是男人的事
Yes, it was a man.
但沒成
But, it didn't work out.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
真是可惜 我很喜歡他
Yes, it's a shame and I really liked him.
以爲就是他了
I thought that he was the one.
也許下次能找到
Well, maybe next time.
你確定不要吃蛋糕嗎
Are you sure you won't have some cake?
不了 謝謝
Oh, no, thank you.
我只是過來看下你 幷跟你道別的
I just came over to check up on you and to say good bye.
道別?
Good bye?
爲什麽 你要去哪
Why, where are you going?
只是去達拉斯參加一個家具業大會
Oh, just to Dallas for a furniture convention.
理查德也去嗎
Is Richard going with you?
不去 我出差而已
No, it's just a business trip.
理查德得照顧自己一陣子了
Richard will have to fend for himself for a while.
山姆 給我兩杯加冰威士忌
Sam, give me two whiskeys on the rocks.
沒問題 簡
Sure thing, Jane.
你看了今天的報紙沒
You see the papers today?
沒 怎麽了
No, why?
有具尸體在鰻魚河裏被發現了
They found a body in the eel river.
謀殺?
A murder?
或許吧
Maybe.
他的胸口上被刻了一個標志
They found a symbol carved in his chest.
看
Here.
是顆五芒星
It's a pentagram.
又跟巫師有關
It's them witches again.
我也是這麽想的 萊爾
That's what I was thinking too, Lyle.
芭芭拉 就是這樣
So yeah, Barbara, that's everything.
杰瑞死後 警察不停地煩擾我
After Jerry died, the cops wouldn't stop harassing me.
他們什麽都證明不了
They couldn't prove anything.
却認爲是我殺了他
They actually thought that I killed him.
你敢信?
Can you believe it?
總之 你走之後 舊金山之行變得很不愉快
Anyways, San Francisco got to be a really bad trip after you left.
我就是在那時想起你還有套公寓
That's when I remembered you had that extra apartment.
這時間真是完美
Well, it was perfect timing.
我只是很抱歉沒能在場歡迎你
I'm just sorry I wasn't here to greet you.
沒什麽的
That's all right.
雀茜很友好
Trish has been lovely.
我做了很多藝術品
And I've been getting a lot of artwork done.
上周有件事真的震驚到我了
But I had this experience last weekend that really shook me up.
怎麽了 發生了什麽事
Why, what happened?
我遇見了一個很帥的男人
Well, I met this greatlooking guy.
我對他用了愛情魔法
And I used love magic on him.
之後他對我變得很怪
Then he got really weird on me.
他所有的情感都開始流露了出來
All these emotions started flowing out of him.
然後他就真的
Then he got really
病了
sick.
男人不太會控制自己的情感
Well, guys can't handle their emotions too well.
所以他們不喜歡沉重的談話
That's why they don't like heavy conversations.
他大概就是承受不住
It was probably just too much for him.
你給他的愛情與美妙性愛
All the love and the great sex that you were giving him.
我想就是這麽回事吧
I guess that's what it was.
但我說不清
But, I don't know.
親愛的 你得多加小心
Honey, you have to be more careful.
或許你起初就不該亂用愛情法術
Maybe you shouldn't be messing with love spells in the first place, you know.
很高興見到你 伊蓮
Merry meet, Elaine.
祝福你 加恩
Bright blessings Gahan.
我聽到你們在討論愛情法術
I heard you discussing love spells.
伊蓮 你務必小心
You do have to be careful, Elaine.
愛情法術從不會像你想的那樣奏效
Love spells never work the way you think they will.
但值得一提的是 見到你真是太好了 伊蓮
But on a lighter note, it's wonderful to see you, Elaine.
多久沒見了 一年?
What's it been now, a year?
我們必須慶祝下好友重聚
We must celebrate this reunion of dear friends.
感謝無處不在的女神
Thank you goddess everywhere
所賜予我們的祝福
for the blessings that we share.
瓦麗亞 應當被稱頌
Blessed be, Variah.
回家去 巫師們
Go home, witches.
回家吧
Go home.
無視他們就好
Just ignore them.
他們總給我們製造麻煩
They're always giving us trouble.
我不知道這地方對巫師有敵意
I didn't know this town was hostile to witches.
這裏又不是舊金山
Well, it's certainly not San Francisco.
但對于一個小鎮而言 這裏算不錯了
But it's not bad for a small town.
不是所有人都能接受我們實施巫術的方式
Not all of them embrace our methods of practicing witchcraft.
但我不明白現在我們爲什麽要那麽緊張
But, I don't see why we ought to be so uptight now.
想當年 我們都自由地做愛
Back in the day, we all made love freely
張貼巴弗滅海報 沒人會教條地看他們
and put up Baphomet posters and no one was dogmatic
是否是巫師 或撒旦信徒 或泰勒瑪信徒
about whether they were a witch or a satanist or thelemites,
或德魯伊 或威卡信徒 或別的什麽
or a druid or a wiccan or whatever.
而那很有趣
And it was fun.
但我們的課程和魔法圈一直很受喜愛
But our classes and circles have been very popular.
你們都教什麽
What have you been teaching?
我想想 我帶了個新班 教的西卓爾魔法
Let's see, I've got a new class on Sidral magic
芭芭拉也帶了個新班 教的是奧根煉金術
and Barbara's got a new class on organite alchemy.
此外 我們還教主要課程
Otherwise, we're still teaching the staples,
能量基礎 地基靈修
energy grounding, earthbased spirituality,
异教徒手工藝
pagan arts and crafts,
蠟燭製作 大師級法術工藝 古代神秘學
candle work, the spellcraft master class, ancient mysticism,
草藥和香料 當然還有性愛魔法
herbs and spices, and sex magic, of course.
你還教性愛魔法嗎
Are you still teaching that?
教啊 實際上 今晚我們爲情欲舞蹈的力量這堂課
Yes, in fact, we've invited some girls here tonight
請了些姑娘過來
for a seminar about the power of sexual dancing.
舞蹈是女人和女孩的强大力量
Dancing is such a powerful thing for women and girls.
你還跳舞嗎
Are you still dancing?
跳啊 我們有些人會在業餘者之夜跳
Yeah, some of us dance here on amateur night.
你也來吧
You should come.
嗨 芭芭拉
Hi, Barbara.
嗨 加恩
Hi, Gahan.
對不起 我們來晚了
Sorry we're late.
你們好 可愛的兩位女士 請坐吧
Hello lovely ladies, please have a seat.
伊蓮 這兩姐妹分別是星星和月亮
Elaine, this is star and her sister moon.
她們是我們今晚的學生
They're our students for tonight.
姑娘們 這位是我們的好朋友 伊蓮
Girls, this is our dear friend Elaine.
嗨
Hi.
我剛提到舞蹈是女人和女孩的强大力量
I was just pointing out that dancing is a powerful thing for women and girls.
叫你們今晚來見我們
We asked you to meet us here tonight
就是要你們學習學習
so you could learn about that.
你們看到那女孩的力量有多强大嗎
Do you see how powerful that girl is?
這些男人會爲她做任何事
These men would do anything for her.
你們很想自己擁有那種力量吧
Wouldn't you like to have that power yourselves?
那我們開始吧
Then let us begin.
所有女巫都得搞清楚她們的力量在哪
All witches need to figure out where their power lies.
我們覺得一個女人最强大的力量在于她的性
And we feel that a woman's greatest power lies in her sexuality.
我們認爲這種力量幷非罪惡 也非反女性主義
We don't view this power as satanic or antifeminist,
而是女性作爲自然生物的一種禮贊
but as a celebration of woman as a natural creature.
是一個塵世之軀 一種精神實質 一處孕育之所
An earthly body, a spiritual essence, and a womb.
整個巫術歷史都與害怕女性的性相交織
The whole history of witchcraft is interwoven with the fear of female sexuality.
我們被綁在火刑柱上燒死
They burned us at the stake
是因爲人們害怕被我們以非正當手段所勾起的情欲
because they feared the erotic feelings we illicited in them.
後來 人們用婚姻使我們被束縛
Later, they used marriage to hold us in bondage
我們被迫成了女僕 妓女和性愛娃娃
and made us into servants, whores, and fantasy dolls
而我們想要什麽却無人問津
never asking us what we wanted.
他們告訴我們 超理性主義且恬淡寡欲的男人是人的標準
They teach us that a normative human being is a hyperrationalist, stoic male
而女人的情感和直覺是需要被治療的病患
and that women's emotions and intuitions are illnesses that need to be cured.
他們認爲男人和女人是不同的
And they believe that men and women are different
真正的平等就在于這種不同
and that true equality lies in that difference.
我們謀求男女極性
We strive for male/female polarity
幷以女神之身重獲我們的原始力量
and to regain our primal power as goddesses.
我們得用男人能理解的方式
We need to teach men how to love us
教他們怎麽愛我們
using ways they can understand.
所以女神們 使用香水
So goddesses, use perfume,
穿高跟鞋 化妝
wear high heels and makeup,
學會打造吸引人的髮型
learn to dress your hair in attractive ways,
巧妙地展現肉體 幷知道該隱藏什麽
display flesh artfully, and know what to conceal.
做一個母親和一個情人
Be a mother and a lover.
堅定自己的立場 但永遠都要讓男人感覺自己是男人
Stand your ground, but always let the man feel like a man.
用性愛魔法摧毀他對你的恐懼
Use sex magic to destroy his fear of you
將他的心向愛情閘門敞開
and to open his heart to the floodgates of love.
只有那時 他才會開始把你看作是一個人 看到你所有的內在美
Only then will he begin to see you as a human being with all of your inner beauty.
他對愛情敞開心扉之後
Then, when his heart is open to love,
你想和他做什麽都可以
you may do with him what you will.
我愛你 伊蓮
I love you, Elaine.
你知道的 對嗎
You know that, don't you?
我非常愛你
I love you very much.
但你得多加注意
But you need to be more careful.
這周晚餐晚了三次
Dinner was late three times this week.
家裏完全是個猪圈
And that house is a total pigsty.
你知道今早我在床下發現了一條很久前的熱狗嗎
Do you know that I found an old hot dog under the bed this morning?
你爲什麽從不梳頭
And why don't you ever brush your hair?
你得好好照顧自己和這個家
You need to take better care of yourself and of the house.
我都不好意思請人來做客
I'm embarrassed to have people over.
之前 我一直很有耐心
I've been really patient up until now,
女巫飛行軟膏
但你得快點進入狀態
but you need to step up your game.
你真是個瘋婊子
I have a crazy bitch for a daughter.
什麽
What?
你沒瘋
You're not crazy.
你沒瘋的話 那你就是傻
Well, if you're not crazy then you're stupid.
是哪個呢
Which is it?
你是瘋還是傻
Are you crazy or are you stupid?
你可以瘦掉幾磅的
And you could lose a few pounds.
你看上去有點胖
You're looking a little fatty.
天呐 伊蓮 你瘦了好多
Oh my god, Elaine, you've lost so much weight.
你現在的身材太棒了
You have such a hot body now.
你喜歡我這樣摸
Do you like it when I touch you like this?
還是這樣摸
Or like this?
我想讓你高潮
I wanna make you come.
別害怕 伊蓮
Don't be frightened, Elaine.
我絕不會傷害你
I would never hurt you.
我不是大壞狼
I'm not the big, bad wolf.
你得有絕對的愛和絕對的信任
You need to have perfect love and perfect trust.
你有勇氣嘗試嗎
Hast thou the courage to make the assay?
我有兩樣東西 絕對的愛和絕對的信任
I have two words, perfect love and perfect trust.
協助我建好
Assist me to erect the ancient altar
在過去做禮拜儀式的古代祭壇
at which in days past all worshiped.
在舊時代 女人就是祭壇
From the old times, a woman was the altar.
聖地是魔法圈中心內的點
And the sacred place was the point within the center of the circle,
即萬物的起源
the origin of all things.
因此 我們應該崇拜它
Therefore, should we adore it.
早上好 格裏夫警長
Good morning, sergeant Griff.
恭喜升官
Congratulations on your promotion.
謝謝 康妮
Thanks, Connie.
有咖啡嗎
Is there any coffe?
有啊 我剛做了些
Yeah, I just made some.
按你喜歡的口味做的
I made it just the way you like it.
有什麽事是你做不好的嗎
Is there anything you don't do well?
有機會就試試我 自己去發現咯
Why don't you try me sometime and find out?
咖啡怎麽樣 史蒂夫
How's the coffee, Steve?
太濃了
Uh, too strong.
我喜歡濃的
Well, I like it strong.
男人畢竟要在工作中保持清醒
Man's gotta stay awake on the job after all.
爲什麽 你一直要忙到深夜嗎
Why, have you been keeping late nights?
或許吧
Maybe so.
可你現在已經升官了
But, now that you've been promoted,
或許你該開始考慮安頓下來了
maybe you ought to start thinking about settling down.
我? 你開玩笑吧
Me, you kidding?
梅多斯警長 一位女士有事找你
Sergeant Meadows, a lady's here to see you.
我是雪莉·柯蒂斯
I'm Shelly Curtis.
我打電話說過韋恩·彼得斯的事 失踪的那個教師
I phoned about Wayne Peters, the teacher who disappeared.
是的
Yes, of course.
坐吧 柯蒂斯小姐
Have a seat, miss Curtis.
你說你覺得彼得斯先生可能被綁架了?
You say you think Mr. Peters might have been kidnapped?
沒錯 他有兩周沒被人看到了
Yes, no one's seen him for two weeks.
我去了他家 郵件都成堆了
I went by his house and the mail's piled up.
他失踪的那天 我們一起吃過午餐
We had lunch the day he disappeared.
我看見他在廣場旁邊和一個陌生女人開車走了
I saw him drive away with a strange woman near the Plaza.
你知道他和她會去哪嗎
Do you have any idea where he might have gone with her?
韋恩過周末會去他的林中小屋
Wayne used to spend weekends up in a cabin he had in the woods.
他常在那約會
He used to take dates there.
天呐
Jesus.
嘿 格裏夫 看啊
Hey Griff, look.
我的天
Good lord.
這到底是什麽
What the hell is this?
我不知道
I don't know.
我們得挖開 史蒂夫
We're going to have to dig, Steve.
我知道
I know.
我想你該回屋裏 雪莉
I think you should go back to the house, Shelly.
這蛋糕太美味了
This cake is absolutely fantastic.
真是一頓豐盛的晚餐
And what a great dinner.
謝謝
Thank you.
我喜歡下厨
I enjoy cooking.
但願你不介意我打電話找你
Hope you don't mind my calling you.
有時 獨自一人很難熬
Sometimes it's so hard to be alone.
完全不介意
Not at all.
雀茜外出時 我也會有點寂寞
I get a little lonely, too, when Trish is out of town.
你和雀茜結婚多久了
How long have you and Trish been married?
今年九月就是十年了
10 years this September.
十年?
10 years?
太不可思議了
It's really amazing.
從沒有人愛我像你愛雀茜那樣 沒有人
No one has ever loved me the way you love Trish, no one.
你的丈夫呢
What about your husband?
我的丈夫從沒愛過我
My husband never loved me.
他都迫不及待地想離開我
He couldn't wait to get away from me.
對不起
I'm sorry.
有時我覺得雀茜也想離開我
Sometimes I think Trish would like to get away from me, too.
可憐的寶貝
Poor baby.
真是個可憐的寶貝
Poor, poor baby.
告訴 什麽會讓你興奮
So, tell me, what turns you on?
什麽會讓我興奮?
What turns me on?
從沒有人問過我 讓我想想
Wow, no one's ever asked me that before.Let me think.
你知道什麽會讓我真的興奮嗎
You know what really turns me on?
飛行
Flying.
飛行?
Flying?
是的 開飛機飛行
Yeah, flying a plane.
你不知道那有多棒
You don't know what kinda high it is.
你在上空飛翔 淩駕一切
You're soarin' up there above everything.
掌握一切
You're in control.
太美妙了
How fantastic.
沒錯
It really is.
只有那時我對事物的感覺才會真切
It's the only time I feel really clear about things.
有時我會思考人生 好奇我是怎麽走到這步的
Sometimes I look at my life and I wonder how I got here.
我感覺我的人生在悄然離去
I feel like my life is slipping away
我却還有很多事沒做完
and there's so many things I haven't done.
比如?
Like what?
我從沒有過任何外遇
I've never had any sort of love affairs
也沒有過任何不端行爲
or gotten into any mischief.
我以前常看史蒂夫·麥奎因的老電影
I used to watch those old Steve McQueen movies,
搶銀行那種
you know, the ones where they'd rob a bank or something,
我會幻想自己是那些
and I'd fantasize that I was one of those
瘋狂歹徒的一員 手裏摟著一個性感頽廢的姑娘
crazy kinda gangsters with a sexy, messed up girl on my arm.
也會幻想自己是西部片裏的人 開槍幹服一個鎮
Or those westerns, when they'd shoot up a town
然後去搞當地的妓女
and then go visit the local prostitutes.
我知道這聽上去很傻
It's sounds stupid, I know.
聽上去不傻
No, it doesn't.
很可愛
It's very sweet.
真的嗎
Really?
雀茜不這麽想
Trish doesn't think so.
我這麽說的時候 她就翻白眼
She just rolls her eyes when I talk like this.
那是因爲她不理解你
That's because she doesn't understand you.
我完全理解你
I understand you perfectly.
是嗎
You do?
當然
Of course.
你想有一次污穢的外遇
You wanna have a sordid love affair.
你想有些不端行爲
You wanna get into some mischief.
你是誰
Who are you?
你在對我做什麽
What are you doing to me?
我是愛情女巫
I'm the love witch.
我是你的終極幻想
I'm your ultimate fantasy.
就是這樣
That's right.
史蒂夫 我要去見那個巫醫了
Steve, I'm going out to see that witch doctor.
誰
Who?
金教授
Professor king.
他專攻黑魔法和巫術
He specializes in black magic and witchcraft.
他也許能幫我鑒別一些我們找到的物品
He might be able to help me identify some of the items we found.
那很好
It's great.
你拿到實驗室報告了嗎
Did you get the lab report?
拿到了 似乎是心臟衰竭
Yeah, yeah, it looks like heart failure.
但毒物學測試報告顯示有微量曼陀羅
But the toxicology report showed traces of jimsonweed
也被稱爲惡魔的大麻 劇毒且致幻
also known as devil's weed, a highly toxic hallucinogenic.
難以置信
It's unbelievable.
你要我和你一起去?
You want me to come with you?
不用 就一會兒時間
No, this will only take a few minutes.
你能幫我點個火鶏肉牛油果全麥麵包嗎
Can you order me a Turkey and avocado on whole wheat?
加芥末蛋黃醬?
Mustard, Mayo?
是啊 還要凉拌捲心菜
Yeah and Cole slaw.
謝了
Thanks.
好
Done.
金教授
神秘學研究
梅多斯警長 抱歉讓你久等了
Sergeant Meadows, sorry to have kept you waiting.
很高興見到你 教授
Glad to meet you, professor.
教授 這是我們在韋恩·彼得斯的墳裏發現的瓶子
Professor, this is the bottle we found in a grave of Wayne Peters,
你在報紙上看到的那個
the one you read about in the paper.
真有趣
Interesting, yes.
正如我所料
Just as I thought.
裏面的東西表明這是個女巫瓶
The contents indicate that it's a witch bottle.
女巫瓶?
A witch bottle?
沒錯 女巫製作它們來防範詛咒
Yes, witches used to make them for protection against curses.
她們會用到自己的體液或頭髮這種個人的東西
They'd take something personal like bodily fluids or hair
再混上草藥
along with herbs
和像是針或碎玻璃的尖銳物來嚇走邪靈
and something sharp like pins or broken glass to scare away evil spirits.
女巫瓶經常被發現埋在古老房子的靈車裏
Witch bottles have often been found buried in the hearse of very old houses.
可以假設製作這東西的人是個女巫嗎
Would it be safe to assume that the person who made this was a witch?
非常有可能
It's very likely.
長眠于文明世界的巫術已再次扎根于城市了
Witchcraft, long dormant in civilized places,has taken root again in cities.
每年都有幾次儀式
There have several rituals per year.
其中之一的薩溫節 相當于我們的萬聖節
One of them, Samhain, corresponds of our Halloween.
其他儀式有慶祝夏至的利薩節
Other rituals celebrate summer solstice, Litha,
有慶祝冬至的伊摩爾格節
or the winter solstice, which they call Imolg.
這是巫師團成員親吻著魔鬼屁股來嘲弄基督教儀式
Here the members of a coven kiss the devil's behind in a mockery of Christian rituals.
這是一個崇拜撒旦的邪教在獻祭一個孩子
Here, a satanic cult sacrifices a child.
如今真有這種事嗎
Does this stuff really go on today?
真有
Yes, indeed.
實施人類獻祭的是黑巫師
Those who practice human sacrifice are the black witches
他們舉行鮮血儀式來獲得惡魔般的力量
who perform blood rituals to gain demonic powers
幷隱秘地將成員凝聚在一起
and to bind their members together in secrecy.
執法部門幾十年來一直想把這些邪教徹底根除
Law has been trying to root out these cults for decades
但一直沒成功
but they've been unsuccessful.
還有就是白巫師或威卡信徒
Then there are the white witches or Wiccans
他們通過與大自然溝通來靈療
who commune in nature in the healing spirit
他們有禁止傷害他人的鐵律
and who have a strict law that forbids harming others.
如今的每個城市和農村
Every city and rural village today has pockets
都有一些實施古代儀式的黑巫師和白巫師
of both black and white witches who practice the ancient rites.
我祈求幷召喚你 我們所有人的萬能之母
I invoke and call upon thee, mighty mother of us all.
我祈求你附身于你的這位僕人和祭司
I invoke thee to descend upon the body of this thy servant and priestess.
陰暗與神聖之母
Of the mother darksome and divine
我以這個動作在此委身于你
here I charge you in this sign.
聆聽偉大母親的話語
Listen to the words of the great mother.
她在古代也被稱爲阿爾特彌斯
She, who of old, who was also called Artemis,
阿芙羅狄蒂 凱麗德溫 戴安娜 愛希絲
Aphrodite, Ceridwyn, Diana, Isis,
還有許多其他的名字
and by many other names.
每當你們需要什麽時
Whenever ye have need of anything,
你們要在秘密的地方集合幷崇拜我
then ye shall assemble in some secret place and adore me,
我是所有巫師的女王
who am queen of all witches.
你們這些願意學習所有巫術的人要集合在那
There shall ye assemble, ye who are fain to learn all sorcery.
看啊 所有愛和愉悅的行爲都是我的儀式
Behold all acts of love and pleasure are my rituals.
看啊 我從一開始就和你們在一起了
Behold I have been with thee from the beginning
我到達了欲望的盡頭
and I am that which is attained at the end of desire.
起來吧
Arise.
親愛的 今晚你看上去有點心神不定
You're looking a little tense tonight, love.
怎麽了
What's the matter?
沒什麽 不過是我的愛情生活又大起大落了
Oh nothing, just my usual roller coaster love life.
喝一杯放鬆下
Well, have a drink and relax.
至少對你來說 沒什麽悲慘的
Nothing's that dire, at least not for you.
對你的受害者來說 就另當別論了
It's an entirely different story for your victims.
什麽受害者
What victims?
沒必要跟我裝清白 親愛的
There's no need to play miss innocent with me, dearie.
請別碰我
Please, don't touch me.
祝福你 芭芭拉
Bright blessings, Barbara.
很高興見到你 伊蓮
Merry meet, Elaine.
怎麽樣了
How's it going?
我又沒人好約了
I'm back in the dating pool again.
怎麽了
What happened?
我還以爲你很喜歡你新交往的
I thought you were crazy about that new guy you were seeing,
那個已婚男人
the married man.
沒有 我跟他斷了
No, I broke it off.
他變得很有心事 悶悶不樂
He just became really obsessive, morose,
他變得很陰沉
and his aura became really murky.
他甚至不想做愛了
He didn't even wanna make love anymore.
他就變得像個女人一樣 什麽小事都要哭
He became just like a woman, crying at every little thing.
沒有男人的樣子
There was no polarity.
不過我早該知道會這樣
But, I should have known.
他是雙魚座
He's a Pisces.
親愛的伊蓮 你爲什麽沒回我電話 見不到你我會死
理查德
Richard.
我跟你說了我工作時千萬別來打擾我
I thought I told you never to interrupt me when I'm working.
你想幹嘛
What do you want?
我只是想告訴你我要睡了
I just wanted to let you know that I'm going to bed
還有我在服藥
and I'm taking a pill.
你睡嗎
Are you coming to bed?
不睡
No.
我還有些工作要做
I have some more work to do.
好吧 那明天見
All right, see you tomorrow, then.
月升草藥
魔法藥店
我是警局的格裏夫·梅多斯警長
Sergeant Griff Meadows of the police department.
我想問你幾個問題
I'd like to ask you a few questions.
好的
Okay.
這東西眼熟嗎
Does this look familiar to you?
這是個女巫瓶
It's a witch bottle.
你知道是誰製作的嗎
Do you have any idea who could have made it?
不知道
No, no I don't.
店裏看到過這樣的東西嗎
Ever seen any of these in here before?
看到過 我們有一些女巫瓶
Yeah, we have some witch bottles.
我給你看一個
I'll show you one.
給
Here's one.
這些瓶子有多常見
How common are these bottles?
在一個姑娘開始把它們供應給我們之前 我就沒見過
I've never seen 'em in here before until a girl started supplying 'em to us.
這姑娘是誰
Who is this girl?
她叫伊蓮 伊蓮·帕克斯
Her name is Elaine, Elaine parks.
誰啊
Who is it?
我是警局的梅多斯警長
Sergeant Meadows, police department.
很抱歉打擾你 夫人 但我在查一件案子
Sorry to bother you, ma'am, but I'm investigating a case
我只是想問你幾個問題
and I just wanted to ask you a few questions.
關于什麽的
About what?
這可能是一起凶殺案
Well, it's a potential homicide case.
只是例行核查
Just a routine check.
我想你也許能幫到我們
I thought you might be able to help us.
好的
Of course.
請進吧 警長
Please come in, sergeant.
你說有一起凶殺案
So you say there was a homicide.
太可怕了
How horrible.
誰被殺了
Who was killed?
一名叫韋恩·彼得斯的男子
A man named Wayne Peters.
你認識韋恩·彼得斯嗎
Did you know Wayne Peters?
不認識
No.
這是他的照片
Here's a picture of him.
以前看到過他嗎
Ever seen him before?
沒看到過
No.
我想我幫不了你 警長
I guess I can't help you, sergeant.
再見
Good bye.
帕克斯女士 等等
Ms. parks, wait.
你以前見過這樣的東西嗎
Have you ever seen anything like this before?
這是個魔法瓶
It's a magic bottle.
我自己製作的
I made it myself.
你見過裝有尿的嗎
Have you ever seen one containing urine?
尿?
Urine?
沒見過
No.
我們在韋恩·彼得斯的墳上發現的這個瓶子
We found this bottle containing urine
裏面裝有尿和一個用過的衛生棉條
and a used tampon on the grave of Wayne Peters.
警長 恕我失陪一會兒
Will you excuse me for a moment, sergeant?
帕克斯女士 你是個女巫嗎
Ms. parks, are you a witch?
是的
Yes, I am.
這有違法嗎
Is there a law against that?
沒有 除非你犯了些事
I guess not, not unless you do something wrong.
你覺得成爲女巫就讓我變邪惡了?
Do you think that being a witch makes me evil,
甚至能殺人了?
capable of murder even?
沒有 我不是想說...
No, I wasn't trying to imply...
梅多斯警長 你知道真正的遭受痛苦是什麽滋味嗎
Sergeant Meadows, do you know what it's like to really suffer?
你不得不一直抗爭 直到你累壞了而無法繼續
You have to fight and fight until you're too exhausted to go on.
巫術是我的信仰 警長
Witchcraft is my religion, sergeant.
這種信仰比你的基督教還古老
And this religion, which is older than your Christianity,
它拯救了我的人生
saved my life.
帕克斯女士 有所冒犯的話 我很抱歉
Ms. parks, I'm sorry if I've offended you.
我不是故意的
I didn't realize.
沒關係 梅多斯警長
That's all right, sergeant Meadow.
你可以叫我格裏夫
You can call me Griff.
格裏夫?
Griff?
我知道我以前見過你
I know I've seen you before.
只是不知道是哪見到的
I just don't know where.
我有同樣的感覺
I have that same feeling.
我知道了
I know.
你是牌裏的那個人
You're the man in the cards.
你是我的命運
You're my fate.
什麽叫我是你的命運
What do you mean, I'm your fate?
我做過一次凱爾特十字解讀
I did a Celtic cross reading.
我的未來牌是權杖騎士
For my future card I got knight of wands.
一直覺得那張牌在做未來解讀時出現的話
Always felt that if that card showed up in a future reading,
我就會很快遇見我要嫁的男人
soon meet the man that I'm going to marry.
但我要嫁的男人得喜歡動物
But, the man that I marry has to love animals.
你喜歡動物嗎 格裏夫
Do you like animals, Griff?
喜歡啊 我喜歡動物
Why yes, I love animals.
事實上 我的一個朋友有幾匹馬
In fact, a friend of mine has a couple horses
我非常喜歡
I'm very fond of.
明天我休息
You know, tomorrow is my day off
外出應該很不錯
and it's supposed to be quite nice out.
或許我要去遠離城市的地方騎馬
Maybe I'll get away from the city and do some riding.
你喜歡騎馬嗎 伊蓮
Do you like to ride, Elaine?
廣藿香 你真是個甜心
Oh patchouli, you're such a sweetheart.
我的女孩還好嗎
How's my girl?
我是你的女孩?
Am I your girl?
今天是的
For today you are.
你是我的女孩 否則周圍也沒人能告訴我了
You're my girl and there's nobody around to tell me otherwise.
除了我
Except me.
那是什麽意思
And what's that supposed to mean?
沒什麽意思
Nothing.
那是什麽聲音
What's that sound?
不知道
I don't know.
我們去看看
Let's go see.
現在是夏至了
Now is the time of the summer solstice.
橡樹王的力量在减弱
The strength of the oak king is waning.
冬青樹王爲了綠色少女
And the Holly king stands ready to challenge him
已做好了向他挑戰的準備
for the hand of the green maiden.
戰鬥開始
Let the battle begin.
你的季節結束了 老頭
Your season is over old man.
絕對不會
Oh never.
我會擁有她
I will have her.
絕不會擁有她
Never have her.
絕不會
Never.
冬青樹王 我宣布你是勝利者
Holly king, I name you the Victor.
綠色少女是你的了
The green maiden is yours.
我的女士
My lady
來吧
Come on.
伊蓮
Elaine.
你認識這些人?
You know these people?
某方面來說 是的
Well yes, in a way.
你們好 我們是公平領主和夫人
All hail, fair lord and lady.
歡迎來到我們的小聚會
Welcome to our little gathering.
你們好
All hail.
我們是文藝復興時期的仙人
We are the good people of the renaissance
和中世紀演員 我們正在慶祝仲夏
and medieval players and we are celebrating the midsummer.
不想加入我們嗎
Won't you join us?
當然想 公平領主
To be sure, fair consort.
他們很迷人 對嗎
They are charming, are they not?
是的 相當迷人
Yes, quite charming.
我看到了兩個相愛的人
I see two people in love.
這意味著一場婚禮
This calls for a wedding.
一場婚禮?
A wedding?
是的 一場模擬婚禮 如果你願意的話
Yes, a mock wedding, if you will.
以此向愛神表達敬意
To honor the gods of love.
好吧
Okay.
現在你們已結爲夫妻
Now, ye are wed.
我很爲你高興 伊蓮 他很可愛
I'm so happy for you, Elaine, he's adorable.
我沒戀愛
I'm not in love.
不是說我沒感情
It's not that I don't have sentiment,
只是愛情是柔弱的
it's just that love is soft.
在我這一行 你需要膽量
You need guts in this business.
我見過被開槍致死的男人 因爲他們戀愛了
I've seen guys get shot to death because they fell in love
內心變得柔弱了
and got soft inside.
我希望將來有繼承人
I want an heir some day
我會需要一個妻子
and then I would need to have a wife,
但愛情是另外一回事
but love is something else.
一個男人會被這樣的東西摧毀
A man can get destroyed by things like that.
就好像他不會再是一個男人了
It's like he's not even a man anymore.
我絕不想變成那樣
I never wanna get that way.
你真的愛他時
When you really love him,
那感覺就像烟花 而別的事都無關緊要了
it's like fireworks and nothing else matters.
你喜歡他的所有小怪癖
You love all the little quirks about him.
喜歡他吃麥片的方式
The way he slurps his cereal.
喜歡他嘴巴略歪的樣子
The way his mouth is a little crooked.
他身上的那些細節變成了你的一輩子
Those details about him become your whole life.
你的內心就如花朵一樣綻開了
Something inside you opens up like a flower
你會發現你還能給予更多的愛
and you realize that you have more love to give
你以前從未覺得這是可能的事
than you ever thought was possible.
因爲你越瞭解他
'Cause the more you know him,
你就越愛他
the more you love him.
你越瞭解一個女人
The more you get to know a woman,
你對她的感覺就越少
the less you can feel about her.
起初 她是個不可思議的神秘對象
At first, she's this incredible object of mystery
能滿足你所有的狂野幻想
who fulfills all you're wildest fantasies.
接著 她會開始顯露小缺點
Then she starts to reveal little flaws
一段時間之後 她就變得非常難照顧
and after a while, just gets pretty hard to care.
理想女性只存在于男人的腦海中
Feminine ideal only exists in a man's mind.
沒有女人能做到
No woman could ever fulfill it.
有時 她想更愛你
And sometimes, when she tries to love you more,
給予你更多 你會感覺自己快窒息了
give you more, you feel like you're suffocating,
快淹死在雌激素中
drowning in estrogen.
這是最可怕的感覺
The most awful feeling.
今晚一起吃晚餐嗎 格裏夫
Dinner tonight, Griff?
今晚沒空 康妮
Um, can't tonight, Connie.
改天吧
Some other time.
嘿 格裏夫 那個姑娘 伊蓮·帕克斯 我有她更多的信息了
Hey Griff, I got more information on that Elaine parks girl.
丟我辦公桌上吧
You leave it on my desk.
你不想聽嗎
Don't you wanna hear it?
史蒂夫 警監要我們撤銷這案子
Steve, captain wants us to lay off the case.
你認真的嗎
Are you serious?
他說我們有不煩擾巫師的政策
He says we have a policy of leaving the witches alone.
他說他們在這鎮上生活很久了 他不喜歡惹他們
He says they've lived in this town a long time and he doesn't like to mess with them.
就算殺人也不管?
Even if they murder?
他說他確信韋恩死于心臟病
He says he's satisfied that Wayne's death was a heart attack.
我也這麽認爲
I think so too.
這裏每個人都瘋了嗎
Has everyone gone crazy around here?
至少讓我告訴你我發現了什麽
Let me at least tell you what I found.
伊蓮和她丈夫杰瑞以前在伯克利經營一家有機美容店
Now, Elaine used to run an organic beauty store in Berkeley with her husband, Jerry.
兩年後 他們離婚了
Two years later they were divorced
伊蓮搬到了舊金山 開始在滑稽表演俱樂部跳舞
and Elaine moved to San Francisco to start dancing at a burlesque club
她就在那裏涉足了一個巫師團
where she got involved with a witch coven.
此團有些人離奇死亡 在警方盤問死亡時間後就解散了
The coven broke up after police questioning when some of it's members died mysteriously.
沒多久 伊蓮的前夫死于藥物過量
Soon after, Elaine's exhusband died of a drug overdose
而前不久 他正打算再婚
shortly before he was planning to remarry.
警方盤問了伊蓮
The police questioned Elaine
但他們沒足够證據抓她
but they couldn't find enough to hold her.
如果舊金山警方什麽都找不到
Well, if the San Francisco police couldn't find anything,
那我們要管了幹嘛
what happened there is none of our business.
你認真的嗎
Are you serious?
我想說這女人是個危險人物
I'd say this woman is a dangerous character
你最好注意好她
and you better watch her.
就因爲她是個女巫?
You mean because she's a witch?
這什麽都說明不了
That doesn't mean anything.
她丈夫死于他以前從沒服用過的藥物
No, her husband died of a drug he'd never taken before.
韋恩·彼得斯從哪弄到惡魔的大麻的 你知道嗎
And did you ever find where Wayne Peters got the devil's weed?
這我問過柯蒂斯女士
I questioned Ms. Curtis about that.
他小屋旁 長有惡魔的大麻
There was devil's weed growing near his cabin.
很顯然 他經常試驗毒品
Apparently, he experimented often with drugs.
拜托 格裏夫 你不能把關鍵點聯繫起來嗎
Come on Griff, can't you connect the dots?
我們這有一起可能的謀殺案
We have a possible murder here
而伊蓮是我們唯一的嫌疑人
and Elaine is our only suspect.
我跟你說過我們撤案了
I told you, we're laying off her.
是因爲命令 還是因爲你愛上她了
Because of orders or because you're in love with her?
誰說我愛上她了
Who says I'm in love with her?
別來煩我了
Get the hell off my back.
你過分了 格裏夫 太過分了
You're out of line, Griff, way out of line.
理查德
Richard.
Richard!
理查德
謝謝你來見我 伊蓮
Thank you for meeting me, Elaine.
太孤單的感覺對我來說幷不好
It's not good for me to be alone too much.
我知道你很忙
I know you're busy.
當然
Of course.
我一直想來
I wanted to come.
我忍不住爲所發生的事而自責
I can't help but blaming myself for what happened.
你不能怪自己
You can't blame yourself.
對理查德而言 你是個好妻子
You were a good wife to Richard.
我也想
I tried to be.
我很努力地去取悅他了
I tried so hard to please him,
但我本該更努力的
but I should have tried harder.
他想要的那種女人 我永遠成不了
He wanted a certain type of woman, someone I could never be.
也許你是對的
Maybe you were right.
也許你應該滿足一個男人的幻想
Maybe you should give a man his fantasy.
你這麽說時 我覺得這很差勁
I thought that was so awful when you said that.
也許我一直都太天真
Maybe I was being naive,
原本我真認爲他因爲我這個人而愛我
but I really thought he loved me for me.
可現在 我希望...
But now, now I wish...
你不能再折磨自己了
You have to stop torturing yourself.
你得放手
You have to let go.
我去了次達拉斯 回來後他都變什麽樣了
Remember how he changed after my Dallas trip?
我想他就是在那期間開始有外遇的
I think that's when he started having that affair.
不管她是誰 她讓他痴狂了
Whoever she was she drove him crazy.
對此 我恨死他了
I hated him so much for that.
我想殺了他們兩個
I wanted to kill them both.
我要是發現她是誰了 我會把她撕成碎片
If I ever found out who she was, I would rip her to pieces.
但現在我才明白我原本應該幫助他的
But now I see I should have helped him.
我不知道他會自尋短見
I didn't know that he was going to take his own life.
嘿
Hey,
hey.
不說我了
Enough about me.
你怎麽樣
What's going on with you?
雀茜 我戀愛了
Trish, I'm in love.
他是誰
Who is he?
他是個警探 他是一個女人想要的一切
He's a detective and he's everything a woman could ever want.
他强壯英俊 聰明善良
He's strong and handsome, smart and kind.
我知道他就是那個人
I just know that he's the one.
他還給了我這個戒指
He even gave me this ring.
我管它叫我的魔法戒指
I call it my magic ring.
這不是訂婚戒指 但我知道他很快就會求婚了
It's not an engagement ring, but I just know that he's gonna pop the question soon.
我們第一次來這時 我給你看了我的訂婚戒指 記得嗎
When we first came here I showed you my engagement ring, remember?
我幾乎沒法再看著它了 太痛苦了
I can barely stand to look at it anymore.It's too painful.
我肯定他很快會向你求婚的
I'm sure he's going to ask you soon.
你會是一個美麗的新娘
You're going to make a beautiful bride.
我們相見的第一天
The first day we met,
你羡慕我 因爲我有男人
you were envious of me because I had a man
而你是單身
and you were all alone.
現在反過來了
Now it's the reverse.
生活真是有趣 對吧
Life is funny, isn't it?
雀茜 抱歉 我得走了
Trish, I'm sorry, I've gotta go.
你想和我一起出去嗎
Would you like to walk out with me?
不了 我想待著把茶喝完
No, I'd like to stay and finish my tea.
好的
All right.
保重 親愛的
Take care, love.
嗨 伊蓮 是我
Hi Elaine, it's me.
你把戒指落下了
Yeah, you left your ring here.
你大概上路了 不過我回家時會順路送來
You're probably driving but I'll drop it by on my way home.
一會兒見
See you in a minute.
理查德
用于理查德的愛情法術
生日快樂
獻給世界上最美的女士 她生日了 今晚見 愛你的 理查德
你個婊子
You bitch.
你害死了我丈夫
You killed my husband.
婊子 蕩婦 妓女
Bitch, skank, whore.
你會爲此而被燒死
You'll burn for this.
撞車 撞車 撞車
Crash, crash, crash.
死吧 死吧 死吧
Die, die, die.
哈邦蒂雅啊 用一杯讓人沉醉的愛侶佳釀
Oh Habondia, bind these two
將此二人結合吧
with a heady lovers' brew.
即便他們奮力逃離
Even should they strive to flee
還是會永遠相依
they'll cling for all eternity.
蘇格蘭威士忌
Scotch.
一瓶啤酒 山姆
Bottle o' beer, Sam.
這兩個新來的姑娘是誰
Who are those new girls?
她們根本不會跳舞
They can't dance at all.
而且她們很怪异
And they're weird.
不知道 但客人很喜歡她們
I don't know, but the customers really like 'em.
她們是巫師的朋友
They're friends of the witches.
我以前看到他們一起進來的
I seen them come in together before.
沒錯 巫師
Yeah, the witches.
他們無處不在
They're everywhere.
一杯加奎寧水的杜松子酒 山姆
One gin and tonic, Sam.
加奎寧水的杜松子酒 馬上來
Gin and tonic coming up.
你們看了那個被埋在自己小屋後院的教師的報道沒
Did you read about the teacher buried in the back yard of his cabin?
據說是巫師挖的
They said it was dug by the witches.
我看了 他們在墳上發現了各種巫術製品
Oh yeah, I read about that.They found all kinds of witchcraft things on the grave.
沒錯 我也聽說了
Yeah, I heard about that, too.
瘮人
Creepy.
坐下 伊蓮
Sit down, Elaine.
伊蓮 從實驗室拿回的DNA
Elaine, the DNA came back from the lab.
表明你和韋恩·彼得斯有關聯
It connects you with Wayne Peters.
帕雀茜亞·曼寧來了次警局
Patricia Manning came by the station.
帶了些你的東西來
Some things of yours.
包括這個
Including this.
她說你害得她丈夫自殺了
She said you drove her husband to suicide.
所以 我是個壞女孩
So, I was a bad girl.
你要懲罰我嗎
Are you going to punish me?
你是什麽樣的人 伊蓮
What sort of person are you, Elaine?
什麽樣的病態思維會做這種事
What sort of sick mind would do such things?
你怎麽這麽消極
Why are you so negative?
我誰也沒殺啊
I didn't kill anyone.
韋恩在春宵一夜後
Wayne died of heart failure
死于心臟衰竭
after a beautiful night of lovemaking.
理查德死于他太愛我了
And Richard died because he loved me too much.
這些男人不習慣與我在一起時的深情之愛
These men weren't used to the deep feelings of love that they were experiencing with me.
你是說這些男人死于愛情?
Are you saying these men died of love?
你瘋了吧
That's insane.
法術和毒藥怎麽說呢
What about the spells and the drugs?
你想說巫術與此毫無關係嗎
Are you saying witchcraft had nothing to do with it?
巫術只是集中能量的一種方式
Witchcraft is just a way of concentrating energy.
它只對已經存在的有效
It can only work with what's already there.
我只是用性愛魔法來創造愛情魔法
I just use sex magic to create love magic.
我不知道法術會有多强大
I didn't know how strong the spells would be.
有時得到的愛情强烈得差點嚇到我
Sometimes it's almost scary how strong the love gets.
愛情?
Love?
你知道什麽是愛情嗎
What do you know about love?
你所謂的愛情是一種邊緣型人格障礙
What you call love is a borderline personality disorder
或者更糟
or worse.
別給我做診斷
Don't diagnose me.
也許你是個沒法愛的自戀狂
Maybe you're a narcissist who can't love.
你覺得我病了
You think that I'm sick
因爲你從沒像我一樣愛過
because you've never loved like I have.
我會爲愛做任何事
Well, I would do anything for love.
沒錯 你永遠都得不到足够的愛
That's right, you'll never get enough love.
即使一個男人愛你愛得無法自拔而自殺
Even when a man loves you so much it kills him,
對你來說還是不够
it's not enough for you.
你就像一個無底洞
You're like a bottomless hole.
你把自己打扮得花枝招展 做斯戴佛式妻子做的事
You doll yourself up and do the Stepford wife thing
以爲每個男人都會拜倒在你的石榴裙下
thinking every man is going to fall at your feet.
但你那瘮人的性感小把戲對我不起作用
But your creepy little sexy act doesn't work with me.
我不愛你
I don't love you.
你怎麽能在那吹噓自己免疫愛情呢
How can you stand there and boast about being immune to love?
爲什麽一個女人真摯的愛會讓你如此害怕
Why does the genuine love of a woman scare you so much?
你覺得你這樣活著很優越嗎
You think that your way is a superior way to live?
我認識很多和我有一樣看法的女人
I know a lot of women who feel the way that I do.
只有男人會讓我們爲了你們的愛而非常努力地工作
Only men make us work so hard for your love.
只要你們是因爲我們這個人而愛我們
If you would just love us for ourselves,
但你不會
but you won't.
我的前夫就像你一樣
My exhusband was just like you.
他對我抑制他的愛 以此來懲罰我
He used to punish me by withholding his love from me.
我這輩子一直在被扔進垃圾堆
All my life I've been tossed in the garbage
除了男人想用我身體的時候
except when men wanted to use my body.
所以我决定要找到自己的力量
So, I decided to find my own power.
我通過巫術發現了我的力量
And I found that power through witchcraft.
這意味著我能從男人那裏拿取我所需要的
That means that I take what I need from men
而不是反過來
and not the other way around.
對不起 伊蓮
I'm sorry, Elaine.
這次不會有效果了
It won't work this time.
我恐怕我得逮捕你
I'm afraid I'm going to have to arrest you.
因爲什麽呢
What for?
根據我的信仰來嫁給情人?
Marrying a lover according to my religion?
勾引有婦之夫?
Seducing a married man?
我知道400年前你會因爲這種事而被燒死
I know 400 years ago you could be burned for a thing like that,
但如今不會了
but not today.
沒錯 不會被燒死了
No, not burned,
但你會因非法埋葬韋恩·彼得斯而被抓
but you'll be booked for burying Wayne Peters illegally
我們還會進一步調查
and we'll find out more.
就是這個女巫殺了那教師
That's the witch who killed the teacher.
你不用爲遭受一個女巫而活
Thou shalt not suffer a witch to live.
燒死女巫
Burn the witch.
燒死女巫 燒死女巫 燒死女巫...
Burn the witch, burn the witch, burn the witch...
燒死女巫 燒死女巫 燒死女巫
burn the witch, burn the witch, burn the witch.
燒死她
Burn her.
Burn.
可憐的寶貝
Poor baby.
真是個可憐的寶貝
Poor, poor baby.
別擔心 一切都會好的
Don't worry, everything will be okay
因爲我好愛你
because I love you so much.
我愛你 伊蓮
I love you, Elaine.
除了你 我從沒愛過任何人
I've never loved anyone but you.
我想和你結婚
I want to marry you.
譯者：微博@Emtee